

Payel Majumder

CPC Certified Medical Coder

My Contact

- mpayel94@gmail.com
- **(L)** +91 7980239334
- 9/1/A, A. K. Mukherjee Road. Kolkata 700090

Hard Skill

- HM Coding
- In Patient
- · ED Coding

Soft Skill

- Observation
- · Decision making
- Communication
- Multi-tasking

Education Background

- Rammohan College (Calcutta University)
 Bachelor of Science
 Completed in 2015
- Mohan Girls' High School (W.B.C.H.S.E)
 Higher Secondary
 Completed in 2012
- Mohan Girls' High School (W.B.B.S.E)
 Secondary
 Completed in 2010

About Me

I have done B.Sc from Calcutta University. I have worked in the medical billing and coding field for over 3.5 years. I have worked for a wide variety of medical specialties including: E/M and Inpatient Professional. I became a Certified Professional Coder in 2022. My certification is still current and I am a member of the AAPC (American Academy of Professional Coders) Member ID 01956278.

Professional Experience

 Project Associate in Medical Coding | DCG Data-Core Systems (India) PVT. LTD.

March 2019 - Present

• Appliance Service | Godrej

April 2017 - April 2018

• Tele Executive | IKF Technologies

2012 - 2015

Achievements

- CPC Certified affiliated by AAPC (American Academy of Professional Coders) in 2022 Member ID 01956278
- Diploma in Information Technology Application (DITA)
 by Youth Computer Training Centre

Hobby

Learning new technologies, Surfing Internet, Listening to music, Social media

Personal Details

Date of Birth: 01-07-1994 Marital Status: Married Nationality: Indian